(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-01T23:15:23.607068",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
Attention For Visitors: Please be aware of flashing lights. Cheering loudly is ok.
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
[Notice: Attention For Visitors]
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
Passing by familiar roads
I couldn't find the reason why
Who I am you couldn't know
Stuck in the ruins, my disillusion
In between a dual reality
My own desire keeps me to you, ooh
Moving faster than the light can
I'm in the absence, alone looking back
Did I lose my way,
I can't see the day
When I can reach you again,
then can I let go?
I can hear your voice leading me through the void
Fade away to the grey
Eternally I'm walking by the lives that flash before my eyes
Alone, the silence deafening, still I'm reaching out to you
Connections sacrificed, the lie I tell myself so I'll survive
One day, eventually the light, it will lead me back, do you see me?
Da da d-da d-da da da - ah ooh
Da da d-da d-da da da I am the wanderer
The concert will be starting soon.
Passing by familiar roads
I couldn't find the reason why
Who I am you couldn't know
Stuck in the ruins, my disillusion
In between a dual reality
My own desire keeps me to you, ooh
Moving faster than the light can
I'm in the absence, alone looking back
Did I lose my way,
I can't see the day
When I can reach you again,
then can I let go?
I can hear your voice leading me through the void
Fade away to the grey
Eternally I'm walking by the lives that flash before my eyes
Alone, the silence deafening, still I'm reaching out to you
Connections sacrificed, the lie I tell myself so I'll survive
One day, eventually the light, it will lead me back...
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
The concert will be starting soon.
Kikkeriki!
Thank you all so much for coming to Takanashi Kiara and Ninomae Ina'nis's 1st Concert Day 2,
Drawn to Dawn!
I am Takanashi Kiara, and next to me is...
Wah!
Good morning, afternoon, evening, everyone! This is Ninomae Ina'nis!
That's right! It is finally time to start Day 2!
Is everyone hyped?!
Hype! Hype! Hype! Hype!
All right. Before we kick things off, of course we have some important safety rules and house guidelines to go over.
First, photography and the use of recording equipment are strictly prohibited during the performance.
However, if you are watching from home, screenshots are allowed. Please take lots of screenshots.
スクショはOKですよ！
Screenshots are OK!
Also, the venue is smoke-free, so please refrain from smoking inside.
Unless you're smoking hot like me!
We haven't heard that one before!
If you start feeling unwell at any... un-feeling well... You start feeling unwell at any point...
...please don't push yourself. Reach out to the nearest staff member for help, and drink water.
For safety, please avoid any dangerous or disruptive behavior.
This, once again, no matter how hype it is, includes moshing, diving...
...sitting on shoulders, jumping excessively, or throwing objects toward the stage, climbing onto the stage, intentionally blocking the aisles or rushing toward the front is also not allowed.
Please refrain from disruptive shouting, erratic lightstick movements, or any extreme motions that might interfere with the experience of those around you. Be considerate.
If you don't follow the instructions of our staff or the venue staff, you may be asked to leave the venue.
Yeah. Please keep in mind that the venue, organizers, performers, and staff cannot be held responsible for any accident, equipment damage, or trouble caused by failing to follow instructions.
So you stumbled over the same words! It's hard, okay? I'm trying my best here. I can't read!
Additionally, any costs for damage resulting from ignoring these rules will be the responsibility of the person involved.
There are cameras in the venue for filming and photography today, and you might appear in the footage or photos.
These may be used for promotional purposes later on, so please keep that in mind.
And finally, just like yesterday, the concert will be in two parts. There's a part for Wawa and there's a part for me, so please look forward to both of them!
And yeah, that is it for the rules!
The show is about to begin, so get ready!
Have fun! Have fun! See you! Bye-bye!
Enlightened by the powers that be,
The ruler of a world run on inasanity.
It's clear to me they still can't see,
I'm just a normal girl,
empowered by the Ancient One's call.
We're gonna be punstoppable, we're not a cult.
Nonsensical and nautical adventures lie in wait!
Gimme a one eight!
Gimme a 1-8!
一！八！タコだち！
One! Eight! Takodachi!
イナイナイナ！イナイナ！
Ina-ina-ina! Ina-ina!
俺のイナの世界線 守るためにタコになろう！！
To protect my Ina's worldline, let's become takos!!
一！八！タコだち！
One! Eight! Takodachi!
イナイナイナ！イナイナ！
Ina-ina-ina! Ina-ina!
いいタコになりますように
Hoping to become a good octopus,
in a sanityで踊りましょう！
let's dance in inasanity!
Think of all that you could be...
We're talking evolution, leave it all to me!
Maybe just a touch of purple ink...
What'cha think?
It's a song you can't ignore,
the Ancient Ones are calling you to be so much more!
Just put your hand in mine and be reborn...
In a blink!
Tell me what those legs are for?
俺のイナ運ぶためです！
They're for carrying my Ina!
You could use six more!
感謝感謝！！ありがたい！！！
Grateful, grateful!! So thankful!!!
We could all get matching ears!
They aren't really ears though...
えー！？
What--!?
Sleepy eyes to fight your fears!
例えばイナいないの世界！！！
Like a world without Ina!!!
Alright, listen to my song, am I striking a chord with you?
Stringing you along so that I don't get bored of you!
80 million strong and we've still got some more to do,
everybody shout!
World domination!!
Can I bank on your emotion? Do I have you invested?
I don't wanna hear you say that you're not interested!
Your unwavering devotion isn't all I've requested!
Do you care? Are you aware that you're my dearest creations?!
Oya oya! A cute little Takodachi found its way right here.
My, my! A cute little Takodachi found its way right here.
Experimentation might be necessary...
Takos... we have to cook!
いいタコだちの作り方！
How to make a good Takodachi!
ひっくり返して丸くして
Turn it over and make it round,
ほらほらまわって 惑わされずに
Turn around and round, don't get distracted!
ちょっとはカリッと 中ふんわりわ
A bit crispy on the outside, soft and fluffy inside,
食ったらそうすべていただき
once you take a bite, it's all mine!
By the power of happy, the ruler of our world run on inane insanity
It's clear to me this girl can't be just a normal girl
Empowered by the Ancient Ones' call, we're gonna be unstoppable, order or chaos
Nonsensical and nautical, a danger lying in wait, let's talk about the future to be
Rewriting all of history in our destiny with cookies as our currency, this priest can finally heal
In a subgroup of nation multiply, or something like takoyaki, no doubt about it
Dimensional traveler, welcome to my world!
いいの！ 最高のDAY！ いいの！ 最高のDAY！ いーな いーな いーな！ いーな いーな いーな！
Good! The best day! Good! The best day! Ina, Ina, Ina! Ina, Ina, Ina!
これのいいの世界線も 守ろう！
Let's protect this good timeline, too!
そう いーなこそ Couture EDEN-1 描く未来... いいな！
That's right, Ina is Couture EDEN-1, drawing the future... How nice!
Ah, with risk of never-ending fun, I'm the world-certified idol
そう いーなこそ Couture EDEN-1 描く未来... いいな！
That's right, Ina is Couture EDEN-1, drawing the future... How nice!
Ah, with risk of never-ending fun, I want the world signed, certified, let's go round and down
いーな いーな いーな... そう いーなこそ Couture EDEN-1...
Ina, Ina, Ina... That's right, Ina is Couture EDEN-1...
私のもの そう 私のもの
It's mine, yes, it's mine!
数百年の財宝
Treasures from hundreds of years ago
この船に眠る
lie sleeping aboard this ship.
Hey everyone! Get ready to rock 5th Fes Day 2! Are you ready?
古びた伝説は
The ancient legend
呪われた幽霊船に
is tied to a cursed ghost ship,
続く夜の兆
a sign of the endless night.
そこに財宝が残る 海賊の夢があるのなら
If treasure remains and a pirate's dream lives there,
ただじゃ置かないでしょ
they wouldn't just leave it alone, right?
挑む者よ
O brave challengers,
若き盗人よ
O young thieves,
命を賭して
stake your lives
この海に返してやろう
and return it to this ocean!
眩いほど 瞳に焦がす 生命の炎
The flame of life burns so dazzingly in your eyes,
秘めた色彩 払う 芳的なのなら
releasing hidden colors—if you are so fragrant...
私のもの そう 私のもの
It's mine, yes, it's mine!
奪ってみろ
Try and steal it!
命の証を あなたの求める全てを
The proof of life, everything that you seek!
輝きは 既に錆び付いて それでも泥にまみれるなら
Its brilliance is already rusted, yet if you still wallow in the mud...
泡沫と共に 沈め
Sink along with the bubbles!
昏い今を耐える
Enduring this dark present,
欲深き海賊の秘宝
the treasure of greedy pirates.
されど笑う
Yet they laugh.
満月の金銀財宝
Gold and silver treasure under the full moon,
七つの海の奥に
deep in the seven seas.
群がる虫ども
Insects swarming around...
孤島の富を狙う
Aiming for the wealth of an isolated island,
愚か者身の程知らず
foolish ones who know no better.
騒がしき墓標を
A noisy gravestone...
群がる 黒い魂の群れ
Ships gathering, a swarm of black souls.
影の底で
At the bottom of the shadows,
忍び寄る者 渦巻く手
creeping ones, swirling hands,
開の閉じた箱
the closed box of the opening.
手放したいわ 諦めたいわ
I want to let go, I want to give up.
悪夢の中から 逃げられるのに
Even though I could escape from this nightmare,
まだ掴んでる
I'm still holding on.
欲望が蠢いたら
If desire squirms...
私のもの そう 私のもの
It's mine, yes, it's mine!
自分自身を信じ込ませてしまって
Making myself believe in it,
縛り付けたとしても
even if I tie it down...
気づいた
I realized
呪いの出口
the exit from the curse.
永遠の夜の中へ
Into the eternal night...
目を覚まして あなたの悪から
Wake up from your evil!
連れ出す舟よ
Oh boat that carries me away,
出港して
set sail.
私のものではない 私のもの
It isn't mine, yet it's mine.
漆黒の薔薇 朽ち果てたとしても
Even if the pitch-black rose decays,
枯れない魂 今では
a soul that never wilts, even now...
魔の誘惑 永遠の美貌
Demonic temptation, eternal beauty—
そんな幻 追っていたのでしょう
I must have been chasing such illusions.
手放せ 偽りついたかい
Let go, were you bound by falsehoods?
さあ行こう 夜明けに顔向けて
Come, let us go, facing toward the dawn!
曰くを宿した舟
A ship laden with legend,
希望だけ乗せて行く 神は乗らない
carrying only hope forward, with no gods aboard.
さあ...
Come...
風に吹かれて 誰にも気づかれぬよう
Blown by the wind, so no one will notice me,
区別がつかない モノクロの世界
in an indistinct, monochrome world.
色を足しても 何も見えなくて
Even if I add color, I can't see anything,
まるで私は 息を止めていた
as if I'd been holding my breath all along.
もういいよ 遠くても 叶えたい
It's okay now; even if it's far, I want to fulfill it.
私は 孤高の世界
My solitary world,
迷いも 抱きしめていたいのに
even though I want to embrace my doubts...
夢のキャンバスに 描き続ける意味は
The meaning of continuing to paint on the canvas of dreams
この胸に 輝いている Story
is the story shining within my heart.
流れることに 意味などないけれど
There's no meaning in simply drifting along,
拾い集めた
yet the fragments I collected,
欠片失うの
am I losing them?
そして夜は その冷たさを 溶かして
And so, the night melts that coldness,
手を伸ばした
and I reached out my hand.
もういいよ 遠くても 届けたい
It's okay now; even if it's far, I want to reach you.
私は
I want to...
ぬくもり抱く 涙も 抱きしめていたいのに
embrace warmth and even hold my tears tight, yet...
夢のキャンバスに 心込めるのは
Pouring my heart onto the canvas of dreams
この空に 描き出していく Story
is the story I paint across this sky.
そして夜は その冷たさを
And so, the night melts that coldness,
溶かして 手を伸ばして
as I reach out my hand.
もういいの 遠くても 叶えたい
It's fine now; even if it's far, I want to fulfill it.
私の 孤高の世界
My solitary world,
迷いも 言葉で包んだ
wrapping even my hesitation in words.
夢のキャンバスに 色を足していく
Adding colors to the canvas of dreams,
この胸に 今輝いて
now shining within my heart.
強くなくてもいい 壊れかけてもいい
It's okay not to be strong, it's okay if I'm falling apart,
この心は 遠くに羽ばたいて
this heart flutters wings into the distance.
響くように 塗り替えていく
So it resonates, I will repaint...
パレット
...the palette.
Hello everyone!
It is Day 2 of 5th Fes!
Yes, yes, welcome to Day 2 of hololive 5th Fes Capture the Moment stage 1 concert!
Are you guys enjoying the show so far?
Yay!
You know, I was really... I want to talk about "Violet" first, because...
Yesterday, I heard you guys sing along to the instrumental,
and I was like, ah, uh, I feel bad for not being on Day 1,
but you know, I knew I was opening for, you know, Day 2, so I couldn't have thought of a better song to open than "Violet", so...
Hope you guys had fun singing it! Thank you again!
And of course, I sang two of my senpais' songs:
Sencho's "Dead Man's Chest" and Towa Senpai's "Palette".
I specifically wanted to choose their songs because...
...they're senpais that I really look up to, and...
I always feel like my journey here wouldn't have been possible if I didn't discover my senpais many, many years ago.
And I always wanted to pay respect to the path they paved for us, so yeah, I hope you guys enjoyed it!
I'm so nervous again!
Yeah, and you know, I of course didn't really tell you guys specifically what penlight colors to use, but I knew you guys would get my message cause we share a brain cell, right? Right?
Yeah, so, well, now going by the different setlist, cause we have different setlists for Day 1 and Day 2...
So, going by the process of elimination, we have a couple of songs from my new EP... Actually, who here bought my EP?
Yay! Thank you so much! I hope you were lucky to get an autograph.
I tried to sign as much as possible, but I knew, you know, sometimes you can't be lucky.
Thank you, thank you! But yeah, I want you guys to have even more fun than before today. I mean, you always have fun, so that's good, but...
Yeah! Now, you know, sing along, have fun,
and I always think that a live stage is where not only me performing is creating the performance,
but you guys as well! You really help, you know, help everyone with that special experience.
So let's create an unforgettable memory together today, okay?
Yay!
Anyways, I would also like to shout out to those watching at home and at the live viewings in the theater! Hello! Hello to you again!
And also, the lovely, lovely girls doing a watch-along right now! Hi, guys! Thank you ID, EN, and everyone else doing a watch-along! Thank you, thank you!
You know, I'm always amazed by everyone's support,
and really, without the support of HoloEN members as well, I wouldn't have had the confidence to stand here today.
Thank you! I love you!
And of course, I would like to remind you guys about the hashtag for today's concert as well, #TakoTori1stConcert, as usual.
Post your thoughts about it, post the screenshots—no videos, no videos!
Post screenshots and, you know, Kiwawa and I, whenever we have time, we've been checking the hashtag. And of course, after as well, I want to hear what you guys thought about the live, so, yeah!
Thank you, thank you!
And unlike yesterday, first MC means I unfortunately have to bid farewell to those watching the sneak peek on YouTube. I'm sorry.
But if you want to keep the party going, head to the streaming site via the description or comment—I don't know where the comment is.
Yeah! But I know that some of you guys won't get a chance to see my new outfit that I revealed yesterday. So I thought, maybe...
Maybe you guys can help me transition into the new costume here, so that even those of you...
So, on YouTube...
chiramise can see.
All right, so I'm gonna count down from 3.
Count down with me, okay?
And I will switch into the new outfit for you guys to see.
Ready?
Ready? Give me a 1 if you're ready!
All right, all right, all right.
All right, here we go.
3, 2, 1, ha!
Tada!
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
All right, it's time to move on to the next song.
And I think this song also fits the starry stage perfectly.
No, not that one yet, but...
But this one is from one of my favorite franchises.
So I hope you guys listen.
Anyways, the song will fit the starry stage perfectly.
Please give it a listen.
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.
The sneak peek part of the show has ended.
Thank you for watching!